<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Recycler View</string>
    <string name="news_content">A landslide occurred in the Summer Hill region of Himachal Pradesh Shimla on Wednesday, as confirmed by an official.
        A landslide struck Himachal Pradesh\'s Shimla, confirmed an official. A search and rescue mission, involving sniffer dogs and personnel, began following the incident. SDM Shimla (Urban) Bhanu Gupta stated that locals believed 21 individuals might be affected. Twelve bodies have been recovered in the last two days. The operation involves NDRF, SDRF, army, police, and home guard. If there\'s hope of survivors, efforts will be focused on their safe rescue.A massive landslide was reported in Shimla\'s Summer Hill area on Wednesday, an official said.
A search and rescue operation was launched after the word of the incident got out and sniffer dogs and rescuers were at the spot at the time of filing this report.

There were no immediate reports of any casualties or injuries in the incident.

Further updates are awaited.

Earlier, on Tuesday, the Indian Air Force airlifted 18 army soldiers in a single sortie to aid the rescue operation following landslides in Shimla.

A Chinook helicopter of Western Air Command airlifted 18 Indian Army personnel and a 3-Ton Mini Dozer in a single sortie for rescue efforts in areas affected by landslides near Himachal Pradesh\'s Shimla today,the Indian Air Force informed through a statement on Tuesday.

Incessant rains continue to wreak havoc in parts of Himachal Pradesh, resulting in damage to buildings and properties.

On Tuesday, 5 to 7 houses collapsed in Shimla\'s Krishna Nagar area following a landslide.

According to officials, some residents were feared trapped in the debris, and NDRF, SDRF, and state police personnel were leading the rescue operations.

Our primary focus is to rescue more and more people. One casualty has been reported so far. All agencies are working to save lives. About 10-15 houses have been vacated and the occupants shifted to safe places. The loss of property is yet to be ascertained, Shimla SP Sanjeev Gandhi said earlier.
    </string>

</resources>